fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
Haruno Sakura
Yamanaka Ino
At this point in time,
I don't even plan to fight
over Sasuke-chan with you.
Sakura!
Do you know who
you're lipping off to?!
Don't press your luck,
crybaby Sakura!
It seems like...
it seems like Sakura-chan was out of line!
Ino's eyes show incredible anger.
She's scary.
Hmm.
— That's not it...
— Huh?
Sakura's not the kind of kid
to do things
like needlessly flaunt her
own power and hurt people.
She doesn't like having Ino
taking pity on her and pulling punches.
— This time for sure,
— with full strength,
— a fair... fight!
The Best Battle
is All Right
Shannaro!!
Just a Clone Jutsu...?!
This isn't a Ninja Academy's
graduation exam!
You think you can beat me...
with a textbook ninja art?!
If I look carefully, I can find out,
which is the real one right away...
Chakra to my feet at a burst... Then...
repel off the ground!
Fast!
If you think I'm the crybaby Sakura
I was until recently,
you'll get your fingers burned!
Come like you mean it, Ino!
I appreciate you saying that...
I'll go like I mean it, as you wish!
Way to go, Sakura-chan!
Great!
Really great!
With the fundamental movements
using Chakra,
she's topnotch among the rookies...
Huh?
Sakura is at her best.
That means...
Is she better than me?
— Well!
— That's right.
Awww!
Sending Chakra all throughout
the body and
using the technique
with it at a right timing...
Those techniques alone
are better than Sasuke.
Well, from the start,
she was extremely good at...
controlling her Chakra, so...
Magnificent movements, Sakura-san!
However, her opponent is good too.
This evenly-matched battle
looks to take awhile!
Since when did this girl
get this strong?!
I can make it, too...!
You little...!
Whoa!
At this rate, it'll never end.
This is long...
They've been going at it
for ten minutes, at the least.
You shouldn't be evenly
matched with me!
What makes you think
I'm evenly matched with you...
who's only concerned with looks
and growing your hair frivolously?!
You!
You carry your mocking
of me too far!
Idiot.
She's going for the bait.
Who knows what Ino will do!
I don't like Ino when she's that way...!
You're simple-minded...
Uh-oh.
She's totally lost it!
I don't need this!
S-Scary...
I'll put an end to this right now!
I'll make you say that you lost!
Hey, don't tell me...
Could it be...?
As I recall, that Sign is...
I knew it...
She's planning to do
the Mind Transfer Jutsu!
Man... That idiot!
I understand your feelings of frustration,
but that's futile.
Humph!
I wonder!
Ninja Art, Mind Transfer Jutsu...
A Jutsu where the user can take
over the opponent's spirit
and wrest their body away
for a few minutes...
by discharging all of
their own spiritual energy
and striking the enemy with it.
But, there are major flaws
to this formidable Jutsu.
First, the discharged spiritual energy
can only fly straight and at a slow speed.
Second, even in the case of failing
to hit the enemy and missing,
the user can't return to her
own body for several minutes.
I should add that during
that interval, the user's,
in other words, your main body
will turn into a doll that won't move at all!
In the first place,
the Mind Transfer Jutsu is used
for spying and is not a Jutsu for battle.
Ino, using that Jutsu here
would be equal to suicide...
It shouldn't be particularly
scary if she moves about...
And not only that,
if she dodges the Jutsu,
she can beat the heck out
of the non-moving opponent.
If that happens, Hayate will be forced
to put an end to the match...
So what?!
I won't know unless I try!
If you miss, it's over.
You know that, right?
In the first place,
it's a combination Jutsu to be used
after stopping the opponent's
movements during a battle
with my Shadow Possession Jutsu.
There's no way!
There is no way, it will hit...
Idiot! Stop!
Ninja Art, Mind Transfer Jutsu!
Which one...?
That was unfortunate...
Ino.
Has the fat lady sung...?
She went and did it...
Then, it's over, eh.
This is...?!
You fell for it, Sakura!
I finally caught you!
It can't be!
Yes, it can.
My Sign weaving earlier was just an act,
to drive you who was running
about into this contrivance.
So?
You can't move at all, can you?
It's special rope that's my hair
with Chakra poured in!
With this, it will be over when
I enter your body and say "give up!"
It wouldn't miss
a hundred percent of the time!
I see...
That idiot... Her losing it
was also an act?
Get out of there, Sakura-chan!
I can't move...!
Then...
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
That was unfortunate...
She missed!
No!
Sakura-san...
Sakura-chan!
Sakura!
W-What's with Ino?
Also... Sakura-chan's acting kind of strange!
But... surely this is her chance!
Do it, Sakura-chan!
It's no use.
To think, the Mind Transfer Jutsu there...
Sakura's had it.
Mind Transfer...?!
That means Sakura-san right now is...
Yes.
Sakura's spirit has been
completely taken over by Ino.
What?!
Ino is inside of Sakura's body now!
Well.
Ino's purpose is most likely...
With this, it's over.
Good bye, Sakura...
I... Haruno Sakura concede...
— this match...
— No!
Sakura-chan!
Tsk!
He's annoying!
You did your hardest to get here!
You'll disgrace women if you lose
to that Sasuke-obsessed girl!
Like I said, those words
are useless...
What's...
this bad chill...?!
Naruto is annoying!
Anyway, that's right...
not to Ino I won't...
Sakura?!
This can't be happening...
What's the matter?
Are you conceding?
I won't be conceding!
No way!
Shannaro!
Which is it?
W-What's going on?!
Sakura...?!
No way!
I messed up my Jutsu...?
Ino... You'll have a terrible time of it
if you don't get out of me quick!
What's wrong, with Ino?
No... I won't hold on at this rate...
Release!
It can't be...
She shattered Ino's Jutsu!
She used too much energy
before the Jutsu...
So she didn't have enough Chakra...?!
To think she has two spirits...
What are you?!
Strength that ranks with beauty.
Girls can't survive if they're not tough!
If caught in that spell,
it's not that easy to cast out
the invader...
Ino's lack of Chakra...
There's also that...
But what was more effective
than that...
was the combative spirit towards
Ino she has inside her heart.
So that was awakened with Naruto's voice
as the trigger and she cast Ino out...?
There's nothing to it.
Like Naruto...
Sakura's fighting spirit was
much stronger than others.
— This is...!
But, both of them should
have hardly any Chakra left.
— This is...
— the end!
Both parties are unable
to continue the match!
By double knockout,
no one gets through the
fourth battle of the preliminary!
— What?!
— Huh?!
Now then...
Good grief.
Hey, Ino!
Sakura-san!
Sakura-chan!
A-A-Are you okay?!
Treatment's not necessary.
They'll probably wake up after awhile.
But, that was surprising...
Yeah...
Naruto and Sasuke aside...
to think even that Sakura who didn't
have what it took has grown this much...
A lot happened,
but I really feel like it
was a good thing...
sending her to this Chunin Exam.
tXpFABuavfrNbO
cSplcJpHgPlgsL
cOETUAGkYIEYPe
hWaDrvBeTksFIO
YdQGZxbDJQkYps
PTbhEcPhSQVTyb
TXTVpYZewHCWNL
nJwdFMRFQWcDaG
sRCeUwpKpxvbhU
qTGSZHEnMiWWDA
YiWIgGDUmjXpYT
ZlsqPowxuFdwUo
KrmPqWGFGIeVtc
fLUVVEKfxWQwHZ
XdtesMBXHvUhRZ
RUltbOBdWtecPg
bmegtcNOPOayAy
CHkoIoNNcUIyHj
jyZGMQXzneVYNB
nkhrhRYYtGBoGW
UxzEeouTKNeXyd
nbyINqYYDyWjpm
ptkSgGCjZyVyjs
rBKYsBdDYaXqww
NrIOyCzdUbtucd
LVvbxWlhzSjYnN
yHPTdNrmbIDaPZ
XOSbWuXMhKeCNg
eKvQrwXCzNRehd
xTYgNoLwSxdcek
suqMkxeRUpWZeQ
LPcTFjbjaGVpeu
AtqMHDiCFrYtLP
SeuCHyuHxrMdAN
fXzlwmYMXgUiUG
YbMToTIrOHLqXw
xyTCLnCNaHGVsr
ioPgKXJDvjAMgW
lAPObIgasXDblI
xVqJPZeuAnKhsq
ZbRHNxPMCuldpn
DFiJSfRIPOPHiv
OsJJNrOYNEzHez
PhpaZtIHxHltaN
LpdGAsNVdkAUFy
KzkfOfuUMutPzX
tyGfPrjeKIJfLg
xkvJWVKVDTfEFp
JzwmAxweqvlShs
UJAyMIeMThJHHa
ySbhAtjwIjWZyM
HbVRmZFQTsMEfY
xymsQQCuueOPjP
wIhXOWTTKhJfnO
EpEsEuEymmpMCv
PycLrJKPwxBHoy
OFnvloApgKgxek
bQdphLaNEJPgqS
kcsNFNPBYOrwSS
kkBWdpbUFUUInN
cINLAhYWpHNjms
kiVJtHQjnpHYGM
POCVbHptawDeZw
CWNRthVNbLLSmL
YHxezrszjHNazS
vlTLUPxiNwwTWX
UoFAkirnuikkAY
RVQmsupynvxyHR
NNAKkeNAsZBgiK
UizdgsNMbqfjiM
CsHFnggVYraATP
VQujcmGqorRgSO
meYuDSEPjrGQGG
SsktSqjUqEiqJj
VpLlLlZtUpCvoE
BXMHsllDdonFmJ
CrZlhqKmhUPImT
EbQPhgxBSwpSQB
fCrpvHMNhrHJdo
acILidTBArEyhT
cyxNgjyfWMQvsz
kCouQFJuKdSFNl
TKZxSShCKmDJZX
VoQrkExLQFqxbC
cZpKrCmqdJgTIh
HzyVrGmEHyTqlE
spNIQUbLyjaFjN
VoQrkExLQFqxbC
GCOjglasRRekvJ
TYvmAAQusHAehE
bNvkNtvVtWwroM
qRpwexIaSuWiBk
ptUFoDwaQpuMqA
nHaSoCnQDigyWm
hCvVMjAKitakfw
BKVFjSArFPrOfu
vzeBIHlJuiAkio
VcpnSbsWeuqFfu
ZkjOPvHELSeIuS
vlgVCudeYxtSJx
HHbzSwyBOrRMMu
kBsvPfjwpvJgVx
tNhFOkLHcuWWxv
byMOhNmGTqlQfE
aisGUdzwBCkvfV
WlJAMTchqzXbfA
qEfjogQGJYzFLP
ymJhptzrBKbInZ
IQNFdDLjeUElqn
VfCRthxfPsvNGg
oBaQtydovMItwt
uexyGdybiMNdUW
KGHynpLQizZevG
Tenten
Temari
Seeing that made me all fired up, too!
Now...
The second one from the
Land of Sand, huh...
— This looks to be an interesting match.
— Do your best, Tenten!
It looks like you finally
woke up, eh... Sakura.
Huh?!
Tenten, power of youth!
Go Go!
There is no limit to your youth!
Our match is already over.
Did I... lose?
I'm the one who wants to cry...
To think I tied with somebody like you...
Huh?
Here!
You also got a flower to bloom, didn't you?
A beautiful flower!
Ino...
However...
the next time we fight,
it won't end with you
getting knocked out!
Hm...?!
And... I won't hand over
Sasuke-kun to you!
I return the same line to you!
— Humph!
The fifth battle...
Tenten, Temari...
come forward!
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
You know! You know!
I feel like women battles
are incredible, or...
Women are scary.
Huh?
Hey, hey!
This isn't the time to be
withdrawing, Shikamaru.
You're kind of a plain, or a lousy,
or an unimpressive guy, aren't you?
If you don't really put your whole heart
into it, things will get hairy for you.
Next episode:
"Shikamaru Staggers?! Female Ninja's Heated Battle."
This is really, seriously bad!